<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

    <title>david.mn</title>
    <link href="http://david.mn/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="http://david.mn"/>
    <updated>2011-10-05T23:22:41-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://david.mn/</id>
    <author>
        <name>David Michael Nelson</name>
        <email>davidmichael.nelson@gmail.com</email>
    </author>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Adding more content for testing</title>
        <link href="http://david.mn/2011/10/02/just-a-test.html"/>
        <updated>2011-10-02T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
        <id>http://david.mn/2011/10/02/just-a-test</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One morning, when Gregor Samsa woke from troubled dreams, he found himself transformed in his bed into a horrible vermin. He lay on his armour-like back, and if he lifted his head a little he could see his brown belly, slightly domed and divided by arches into stiff sections. &lt;strong&gt;The bedding was hardly able to cover it and seemed ready to slide off any moment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His many legs, pitifully thin compared with the size of the rest of him, waved about helplessly as he looked. &lt;em&gt;&amp;#8220;What&amp;#8217;s happened to me? &amp;#8221;&lt;/em&gt; he thought. It wasn&amp;#8217;t a dream. His room, a proper human room although a little too small, lay peacefully between its four familiar walls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A collection of textile samples lay spread out on the table - Samsa was a travelling salesman - and above it there hung a picture that he had recently cut out of an illustrated magazine and housed in a nice, gilded frame. It showed a lady fitted out with a fur hat and fur boa who sat upright, raising a heavy fur muff that covered the whole of her lower arm towards the viewer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gregor then turned to look out the window at the dull weather. Drops of rain could be heard hitting the pane, which made him feel quite sad. &amp;#8220;How about if I sleep a little bit longer and forget all this nonsense&amp;#8221;, he thought, but that was something he was unable to do because he was used to sleeping on his right, and in his present state couldn&amp;#8217;t get into that position. However hard he threw himself onto his right, he always rolled back to where he was.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Welcome to 'Davidmn'</title>
        <link href="http://david.mn/2011/09/23/first-post.html"/>
        <updated>2011-09-23T00:00:00-03:00</updated>
        <id>http://david.mn/2011/09/23/first-post</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Davidmn is going to be an awesome project. Etiam porta sem malesuada magna mollis euismod. Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aenean eu leo quam. &lt;em&gt;Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, &lt;em&gt;nisi erat&lt;/em&gt; porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    </entry>
    

</feed>